joined.com 2015-03-29

# Professional Profile | Joined.com

**Joined Software Solutions Inc.’s Privacy Policy**

The following policy sets forth how Joined Software Solutions Inc., ("JSS ") collects, uses and discloses the information about JSS members and their authorized representatives (“Members”) that JSS collects on this website (“Member Information”). This policy applies to [www.joined.com](http://www.joined.com/) and any websites related to operation of the JSS Services (“JSS Services”). By using or accessing JSS’s website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collected.**  
During the Member registration, JSS collects identifiable information, including, but not limited to, name, company name, work address, email address, phone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information, JSS reasonably requires in order to provide access to JSS’s software applications and services to its Members. Members who use the JSS Services select or are assigned user names and passwords, all of which are used to identify the Members when they are using JSS Services.

JSS collects email addresses of non-Member visitors (“Client Email Lists”), who have provided their email addresses to Members for, among other things, the purpose of receiving communications, from such Member for the purpose of providing JSS Services. JSS does not collect names, postal or email addresses, and phone numbers of non-Member visitors to JSS's Web site, except to complete pending registration applications, to provide access to product demonstrations, or to respond to inquiries regarding the JSS Services. 

JSS also collects information necessary to facilitate sending and tracking electronic mail outs for its Members.

JSS may retain copies of any communications JSS sends to or receives from Members and other visitors to our site for our records, but may not use any such information except in accordance with the terms hereof. 

JSS’s web server collects and saves the default information customarily logged by World-Wide Web server software. Specifically, for each http request received, the date and time, the originating IP address, the object requested, and the completion status of the request is collected and saved.

JSS analyzes these logs monthly to determine the traffic through the server during that month in hits, the number of pages served, and the level of demand for pages of interest during each month. JSS may also analyze accesses to particular pages to determine Canadian versus non-Canadian use, government agency versus private use, and other statistics that may be of value to JSS.

Members post content on the JSS website(s) at their own risk. JSS cannot control the actions of other Members with whom the Member may choose to share pages and information. Therefore, JSS cannot and does not guarantee that Member’s content posted on the JSS’s website (s) will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. Members acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of Member’s content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Members have copied or stored the Member’s content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on JJS’s website(s) is a violation of the Terms of Service and should be reported to abuse@joined.com

**Use of Collected Information.**  
JSS utilizes the information submitted by prospective Members to authenticate and verify the identity of such prospective Members who may be communicating with JSS. JSS will use the information it collects during the registration process, and other information it collects while authenticating the identity of prospective Members to evaluate the Member's application for use of the JSS Services and to conduct security and monitoring.

JSS uses information it collects from Members, including but not limited to the Client Email List, in connection the completion of all mailings on behalf of the Members. JSS may use such information to operate, maintain and enhance the JSS Services and other services offered by JSS. JSS also uses Member information to monitor compliance with the rules and policies of the JSS Services. 

JSS compiles and analyzes its Members’ information into aggregated research reports. Except as may be otherwise agreed in a separate agreement between JSS and any Member, JSS may share this aggregated data with its business partners. 

**Member access, update or deletion of information collected by JSS.**  
Upon written request, JSS will provide to Member a summary of any Member Information retained by JSS regarding the Member. Members have a responsibility to keep certain information current. Members may correct, change or update the Member Information, Client Email Lists and information about their authorized representatives through the use of the Member login and password, as applicable. 

**Information Sharing.**  
JSS and its authorized representatives have access to the Member Information, including the Client Email Lists.  JSS shares Member Information with third parties when JSS has permission from Member or when JSS believes in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. 

Where a Member makes use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on JSS’s website(s), (e.g., sending a personal message to another member or third party; posting content), Member is permitting JSS to share that information.  

Each Member's Mail Tracking Information will contain certain read rate, article open rate and image open rate information that JSS maintains for Members while such Member uses JSS Services. 

JSS may disclose Member Information when JSS has reason to believe that disclosing Member Information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the terms of use for the JSS Services or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with JSS rights or property, other JSS Members, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. 

JSS may share aggregated Member Information with any third parties. From time to time, JSS may retain the services of third-party service providers and consultants. JSS may allow these third parties to access Member Information. 

**Cookies.**  
JSS’s Web site(s) may use cookies to recognize each Member as an authorized user of the JSS Services, and allow JSS to provide customized services and improve the performance and usability of our website(s). JSS may offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Member is always free to decline our cookies if its browser permits, although in that case such Member may not be able to use certain features on JSS’s website(s). 

**Member choices regarding collection, use and distribution of Member Information.**   
By accepting the terms of the terms of use for the JSS Services and becoming a Member, each Member agrees that JSS may collect certain information (as detailed in this Privacy Policy) from and about the Member to authenticate the Member and enroll the Member as a user of the JSS Services. If a prospective Member does not agree to this Privacy Policy, it may not become a Member. 

JSS may offer a Member during registration or, through a follow-on email, the opportunity to receive offers and information about products and services from JSS and its partners that JSS believes may be of interest to the Member. The Member will be provided a choice whether to accept or not accept this offer.  If Member accepts, JSS (or agents working on behalf of JSS) may occasionally send the Member such information.  If this offer is not accepted, then Member will not receive such information.  If Member initially accepts, Member will be provided opportunity to discontinue receiving such information each time it is sent. 

**Member Contact.**  
JSS reserves the right to contact Members regarding account status and changes to the terms of use for the JSS Services, this Privacy Policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to Members. 

**Google Ads.**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Joined.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html).

**Security Precautions.**  
JSS takes protective measures related to information security within the JSS Services to ensure the confidentiality of sensitive Member Information while stored or in use within the JSS Services.

This Privacy Policy covers exchanges of information within the JSS websites and through Member mailings. The JSS sites may contain links to other sites but JSS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. JSS encourages Members to be aware when they leave JSS’s website(s) to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by JSS.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.**  
JSS may change this Privacy Policy at any time and will post the changes to the Privacy Policy on our Web sites. Any change to this Privacy Policy will become effective ten (10) business days after it is initially posted on the JSS Web sites unless otherwise agreed with Member in writing. Continued use of the JSS Services following such period will mean that the Member accepts such changes, which shall also bind its authorized representatives. If a Member does not agree to any such change, it must terminate its agreement with JSS and cease using JSS Services.

**Contacting JSS.**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information collection, use and disclosure practices you can contact privacy@joined.com.
